Tool to Test Your Stool

Tool to Test Your Stool

Privacy Policy
==============

> Please read the [Terms of Use](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/privacy) carefully BEFORE using this website. Your use of this website indicates your acceptance of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. If you do NOT agree with all the terms in the Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy, do not use this website in any manner.
> 
> Last modified: 2016. 12. 01.

### Introduction

When you use StoolAnalyzer.com, you trust us with your information. This Privacy policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. This is important; we hope you will take time to read it carefully.

### What personal information we may collect

When you register as an StoolAnalyzer.com member or contact us, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences.

We may ask for a government issued ID in limited circumstances for the purpose of identity authentication.

### How we use your personal information

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on StoolAnalyzer.com latest changes of terms and policies, website updates, and communicating with customers.

We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our content, services, and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.

We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of StoolAnalyzer.com account holders.

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with StoolAnalyzer.com, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve StoolAnalyzer.com's products, services, and customer communications.

If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

### Collection and use of non-personal information

We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

* We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where an StoolAnalyzer.com product is used so that we can better understand customer behaviour and improve our products, services, and advertising.
* We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non‑personal information for the purposes of this Privacy policy.
* We may collect and store details of how you use our services, including search queries. This information may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services.

### Payment information

Rest assured that StoolAnalyzer.com is not storing your credit card number nor any other financial information related to your payments. When you submit the form, the data is encrypted using payment gateway encryption keys and we cannot access your financial info. We pass this encrypted data to the payment gateway www.braintreepayments.com to complete the processing of the transaction. Braintree is owned by eBay’s PayPal.

StoolAnalyzer.com keeps only information about the date, amount, which member is made a payment and type of membership.

### Cookies and other technologies

As is true of most Internet services, we may gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data.

We can use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behaviour on the site, to improve our product and services, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. StoolAnalyzer.com may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the StoolAnalyzer.com website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

### Disclosure to third parties

At times StoolAnalyzer.com may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with StoolAnalyzer.com to provide products and services, or that help StoolAnalyzer.com market to customers. For example, when you purchase membership plan, you authorize StoolAnalyzer.com and your carrier to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by StoolAnalyzer.com and your carrier’s respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by StoolAnalyzer.com to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

StoolAnalyzer.com shares personal information with companies who provide services such as fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever StoolAnalyzer.com operates.

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for StoolAnalyzer.com to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

We keep the right to disclose entire correspondence with you and make it public if we find it necessary.

### Third party sites and services

StoolAnalyzer.com website may contain links to third-party websites, products or services. We cannot be responsible for the terms or content displayed on those third parties. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

### Modifications to this agreement

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditions at any time and without notice to you. All Privacy policy changes are effective immediately. Your continued use of the site following any Privacy policy changes will mean you accept those changes.

### You May Like

[

Toilet Snorkel](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/toilet-snorkel)

[

Interesting Facts](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/interesting-facts-1)

[

How to Ask](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/how-to-ask)

[

Test Your Stool](https://www.stoolanalyzer.com/select/shape)

An ideal stool looks like a torpedo – it should be large, soft, fluffy and easy to pass.

– _**Dr. Foxx-Orenstein**, president of the American College of Gastroenterology_

There is nothing more natural than pooing. Everyone does it, sometimes several times a day. It doesn't matter if you are young or old, rich or poor, a queen or the president... Even the Pope needs to take a poo. Please visit often to analyze your poo.

Please understand that this program has been designed to help you evaluate and manage your daily diet and routines. It is in no way a replacement for medical consultation. Talk to your doctor if you are concerned about the color, shape, or behavior of your bowel movements.

Users

Info

2009 – 2023 © StoolAnalyzer.com
